[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "I'm awesome, I feel great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "awesome", ",", "I", "feel", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Have they been?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "they", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Yeah, people have been loosing their lives now from this, where these kids around America.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "people", "have", "been", "loosing", "their", "lives", "now", "from", "this", ",", "where", "these", "kids", "around", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "I don't make anything of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "make", "anything", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Have you ever, when you grew up on the streets of Brooklyn, would you ever have done something like that?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", ",", "when", "you", "grew", "up", "on", "the", "streets", "of", "Brooklyn", ",", "would", "you", "ever", "have", "done", "something", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Oh yeah, you know, if I was on a robbing spree as I'm robbing somebody when I was a young kid I've done something like that but this is just for fun.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yeah", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "I", "was", "on", "a", "robbing", "spree", "as", "I", "'m", "robbing", "somebody", "when", "I", "was", "a", "young", "kid", "I", "'ve", "done", "something", "like", "that", "but", "this", "is", "just", "for", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Brooklyn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Why do people do it you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "people", "do", "it", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What do you think the real cares and fears of the average American on the street are right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "real", "cares", "and", "fears", "of", "the", "average", "American", "on", "the", "street", "are", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Healthcare, these people haven't been to the doctor in 20 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Healthcare", ",", "these", "people", "have", "n't", "been", "to", "the", "doctor", "in", "20", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "This thing really, it just really went horrible, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "thing", "really", ",", "it", "just", "really", "went", "horrible", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "I mean the idea behind it, would you be supportive of the idea of bringing millions of Americans into healthcare, who wouldn't otherwise be able to afford it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "the", "idea", "behind", "it", ",", "would", "you", "be", "supportive", "of", "the", "idea", "of", "bringing", "millions", "of", "Americans", "into", "healthcare", ",", "who", "would", "n't", "otherwise", "be", "able", "to", "afford", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "If they can get the healthcare, but as of now it doesn't seem they can get it.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "they", "can", "get", "the", "healthcare", ",", "but", "as", "of", "now", "it", "does", "n't", "seem", "they", "can", "get", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Does it reduce his standing as a President?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "reduce", "his", "standing", "as", "a", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, maybe as a President, I don't know what it takes to become a President.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "maybe", "as", "a", "President", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "it", "takes", "to", "become", "a", "President", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Do you think that's a fair criticism from what you hear on the streets?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "fair", "criticism", "from", "what", "you", "hear", "on", "the", "streets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well listen, we got to stop being involved with the knockout game.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "listen", ",", "we", "got", "to", "stop", "being", "involved", "with", "the", "knockout", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Could be anywhere, right?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "be", "anywhere", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "YSON: It could be in Los Angeles.", "answer_tokens": ["YSON", ":", "It", "could", "be", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "What do you do about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Listen, it was meant that way, that's why the jails are full of us.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "it", "was", "meant", "that", "way", ",", "that", "'s", "why", "the", "jails", "are", "full", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Just more and more guns?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "more", "and", "more", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "White will have guns too.", "answer_tokens": ["White", "will", "have", "guns", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "What is your view about that debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "that", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Hey, people go can do what they want to do in life and have nothing to do about what our community do.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "people", "go", "can", "do", "what", "they", "want", "to", "do", "in", "life", "and", "have", "nothing", "to", "do", "about", "what", "our", "community", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "What is it like being Mike Tyson?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "like", "being", "Mike", "Tyson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Oh wow, now it's pretty interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "wow", ",", "now", "it", "'s", "pretty", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Tyson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Your state of mind?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "state", "of", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "I'm just -- I'm very I don't want to say I'm a complete person by any means.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "--", "I", "'m", "very", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "say", "I", "'m", "a", "complete", "person", "by", "any", "means", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "JJR", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "How hard is it to keep that away?", "question_tokens": ["How", "hard", "is", "it", "to", "keep", "that", "away", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, like that as was explained earlier it's a struggle.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "like", "that", "as", "was", "explained", "earlier", "it", "'s", "a", "struggle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Who do you feel like giving the most thanks to in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "feel", "like", "giving", "the", "most", "thanks", "to", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "TO", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "YSON: Hey.", "answer_tokens": ["YSON", ":", "Hey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "When you finished it, you read the final version what did you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "finished", "it", ",", "you", "read", "the", "final", "version", "what", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I said this is a well done book.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "this", "is", "a", "well", "done", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "How hard is it being for you to be that open?", "question_tokens": ["How", "hard", "is", "it", "being", "for", "you", "to", "be", "that", "open", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well, it haven't been difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "have", "n't", "been", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kirkpatrick"]}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "WP$", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "That's not a subject of humor really is it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "a", "subject", "of", "humor", "really", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "No it's not but the fact is that who is my father is -- whose been in my life for that period in time that I know was, you know Curly Kirkpatrick and that's why I always consider my father.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "it", "'s", "not", "but", "the", "fact", "is", "that", "who", "is", "my", "father", "is", "--", "whose", "been", "in", "my", "life", "for", "that", "period", "in", "time", "that", "I", "know", "was", ",", "you", "know", "Curly", "Kirkpatrick", "and", "that", "'s", "why", "I", "always", "consider", "my", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "They told that you've been doing, How important has it been for you to have that audience's reaction again to work out hear people cheering for you?", "question_tokens": ["They", "told", "that", "you", "'ve", "been", "doing", ",", "How", "important", "has", "it", "been", "for", "you", "to", "have", "that", "audience", "'s", "reaction", "again", "to", "work", "out", "hear", "people", "cheering", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "You know, this is where it's very tricky in this particular situation.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "this", "is", "where", "it", "'s", "very", "tricky", "in", "this", "particular", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "DT", ",", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "It's that the same feeling?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "that", "the", "same", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "There was a time when you were the most infamous fighter on the planet, the most dangerous guy out there and you played up to that, baddest man on the planet and so on.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "a", "time", "when", "you", "were", "the", "most", "infamous", "fighter", "on", "the", "planet", ",", "the", "most", "dangerous", "guy", "out", "there", "and", "you", "played", "up", "to", "that", ",", "baddest", "man", "on", "the", "planet", "and", "so", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "And if I can say to you now, look you can have money and success but you won't be recognized, would you take that option or is there a part of it that you like?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "I", "can", "say", "to", "you", "now", ",", "look", "you", "can", "have", "money", "and", "success", "but", "you", "wo", "n't", "be", "recognized", ",", "would", "you", "take", "that", "option", "or", "is", "there", "a", "part", "of", "it", "that", "you", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Money doesn't mean anything to me, I don't know that's just who I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Money", "does", "n't", "mean", "anything", "to", "me", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "'s", "just", "who", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "How many people do you trust completely?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "people", "do", "you", "trust", "completely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Hey, I'm just, anything I trust complicity is with my wife.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "I", "'m", "just", ",", "anything", "I", "trust", "complicity", "is", "with", "my", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "You've been married only five years?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "married", "only", "five", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Are you proud of that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "proud", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "I'm extremely proud of that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "extremely", "proud", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Do you feel lucky that she came into your life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "that", "she", "came", "into", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Hey, I'm more than lucky, I'm just very grateful as well, you know, and it's just -- it was something I never dreamed that I'd be capable of doing.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "I", "'m", "more", "than", "lucky", ",", "I", "'m", "just", "very", "grateful", "as", "well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "just", "--", "it", "was", "something", "I", "never", "dreamed", "that", "I", "'d", "be", "capable", "of", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Are you difficult to be around?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "difficult", "to", "be", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Hey, I'm -- I can't live with myself so how do you think is going to be easy for somebody else to live with me if I'm really -- I'm very difficult to live with myself.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "I", "'m", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "live", "with", "myself", "so", "how", "do", "you", "think", "is", "going", "to", "be", "easy", "for", "somebody", "else", "to", "live", "with", "me", "if", "I", "'m", "really", "--", "I", "'m", "very", "difficult", "to", "live", "with", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Would you think you would have even made it out of your teenage years without your mother?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "think", "you", "would", "have", "even", "made", "it", "out", "of", "your", "teenage", "years", "without", "your", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Why did you that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Hey, listen, that was partly for me, I don't know why would you that she was dead, how could that -- how could you enjoy that, you know, maybe that's my guilt of being a horrible son.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "listen", ",", "that", "was", "partly", "for", "me", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "why", "would", "you", "that", "she", "was", "dead", ",", "how", "could", "that", "--", "how", "could", "you", "enjoy", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "maybe", "that", "'s", "my", "guilt", "of", "being", "a", "horrible", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Was it your way of thanking her or be it belatedly?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "your", "way", "of", "thanking", "her", "or", "be", "it", "belatedly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Maybe it wasn't thanking her but maybe to tell and show that I love her, you know, but that's how my life has always been, by my love, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "it", "was", "n't", "thanking", "her", "but", "maybe", "to", "tell", "and", "show", "that", "I", "love", "her", ",", "you", "know", ",", "but", "that", "'s", "how", "my", "life", "has", "always", "been", ",", "by", "my", "love", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "Did you ever get the chance to tell her that you loved her?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "get", "the", "chance", "to", "tell", "her", "that", "you", "loved", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I don't know, we didn't have that relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "we", "did", "n't", "have", "that", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "What would you, what would you -- if you had the chance to talk to her again, what would you say to her now at the stage of your life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", ",", "what", "would", "you", "--", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "to", "talk", "to", "her", "again", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "her", "now", "at", "the", "stage", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "But, what did you learn about money?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "what", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Not much.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "When you go around the world, is that one of the things that most people not talked to you about, the Hangover?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "go", "around", "the", "world", ",", "is", "that", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "most", "people", "not", "talked", "to", "you", "about", ",", "the", "Hangover", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Well, the younger kids do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "younger", "kids", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "I was like your fan and stuff and most of the guys run around and ask me what was 2pac like?", "question_tokens": ["I", "was", "like", "your", "fan", "and", "stuff", "and", "most", "of", "the", "guys", "run", "around", "and", "ask", "me", "what", "was", "2pac", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Let me play the commercial.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "play", "the", "commercial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Are you okay?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "okay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well it's great.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "it", "'s", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "So Mr. Rodman, roundtrip to North Korea?", "question_tokens": ["So", "Mr.", "Rodman", ",", "roundtrip", "to", "North", "Korea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "One way.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Rodman"], "LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "That moment when you realized Mike Tyson has decided to eat your ear in the middle of a fight, what goes to your mind?", "question_tokens": ["That", "moment", "when", "you", "realized", "Mike", "Tyson", "has", "decided", "to", "eat", "your", "ear", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "a", "fight", ",", "what", "goes", "to", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Shocked.", "answer_tokens": ["Shocked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Tyson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "I mean, Lewis, when you were watching that, what did you think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Lewis", ",", "when", "you", "were", "watching", "that", ",", "what", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I was horrified.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "horrified", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lewis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "He did?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "So we're both sitting here.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "we", "'re", "both", "sitting", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Did you bite Lennox Lewis' leg?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "bite", "Lennox", "Lewis", "'", "leg", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yes, I did bite his leg.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "bite", "his", "leg", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lennox Lewis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "And you did get any chunk of it to keep or?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "did", "get", "any", "chunk", "of", "it", "to", "keep", "or", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "When you see the video of you biting Holyfield's ear, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "video", "of", "you", "biting", "Holyfield", "'s", "ear", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Holyfield"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "And you deserve the news?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "deserve", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "So you're pleased about that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "pleased", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Big time.", "answer_tokens": ["Big", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Do you get a lot of pleasure now from these young boxers that you're helping to mentor?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "a", "lot", "of", "pleasure", "now", "from", "these", "young", "boxers", "that", "you", "'re", "helping", "to", "mentor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Hey man, you can't imagine.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", "man", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "imagine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "All of them?", "question_tokens": ["All", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "All of them.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "When was the last time?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Haven't been getting arguments now.", "answer_tokens": ["Have", "n't", "been", "getting", "arguments", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Because people must still tried on with you, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "people", "must", "still", "tried", "on", "with", "you", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "No time recently.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "time", "recently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "How would you react if they did?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "react", "if", "they", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I will -- I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "But if you have to, you would?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "have", "to", ",", "you", "would", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I don't want to do it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Do you still work out a lot?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "work", "out", "a", "lot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "I mean I know you use to read lots of books and what kind of things you like to read?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "know", "you", "use", "to", "read", "lots", "of", "books", "and", "what", "kind", "of", "things", "you", "like", "to", "read", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I got a book that's the history of warfare and the histories of all the generals and warfare.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "a", "book", "that", "'s", "the", "history", "of", "warfare", "and", "the", "histories", "of", "all", "the", "generals", "and", "warfare", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Any sportsman from other sports?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "sportsman", "from", "other", "sports", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Man, there's a lot of great other sports to, with a lot of great women athletes too.", "answer_tokens": ["Man", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "great", "other", "sports", "to", ",", "with", "a", "lot", "of", "great", "women", "athletes", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "And was Ali the guy that you would love to have fought?", "question_tokens": ["And", "was", "Ali", "the", "guy", "that", "you", "would", "love", "to", "have", "fought", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "YSON: No way.", "answer_tokens": ["YSON", ":", "No", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "If can now, would you ever get back in the ring?", "question_tokens": ["If", "can", "now", ",", "would", "you", "ever", "get", "back", "in", "the", "ring", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "You're done with that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "done", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Pretty much.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Would you fight Holyfield?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "fight", "Holyfield", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Holyfield"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Does that bother you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "bother", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJR", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Well it is -- I'm not as young as I used to be.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "it", "is", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "as", "young", "as", "I", "used", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Everything that's happened to you that's in this extraordinary book?", "question_tokens": ["Everything", "that", "'s", "happened", "to", "you", "that", "'s", "in", "this", "extraordinary", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Well I never thought about that, just being free again.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "never", "thought", "about", "that", ",", "just", "being", "free", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Why did you like it so much?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "like", "it", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I've never been that free before.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "been", "that", "free", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Actually she was four years old?", "question_tokens": ["Actually", "she", "was", "four", "years", "old", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "TO", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "How did you deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Hey, I used to -- this way, I used to feel like that when I was at the hospital where other people's children had died or was dying as my daughter died and I realized I don't have no exclusives of either pain and I have to handle it like everyone else handled it and try to be a better father for the children that I have living with me now and to the best of my ability and that's just what it is and that's all I can do, unless I can kill myself and deal with the pain that way and I don't think that's the best way to do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "I", "used", "to", "--", "this", "way", ",", "I", "used", "to", "feel", "like", "that", "when", "I", "was", "at", "the", "hospital", "where", "other", "people", "'s", "children", "had", "died", "or", "was", "dying", "as", "my", "daughter", "died", "and", "I", "realized", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "no", "exclusives", "of", "either", "pain", "and", "I", "have", "to", "handle", "it", "like", "everyone", "else", "handled", "it", "and", "try", "to", "be", "a", "better", "father", "for", "the", "children", "that", "I", "have", "living", "with", "me", "now", "and", "to", "the", "best", "of", "my", "ability", "and", "that", "'s", "just", "what", "it", "is", "and", "that", "'s", "all", "I", "can", "do", ",", "unless", "I", "can", "kill", "myself", "and", "deal", "with", "the", "pain", "that", "way", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "'s", "the", "best", "way", "to", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "What do you say to them as a father?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "them", "as", "a", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Hey listen, whatever situation arise I try to help them to the best of my ability.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", "listen", ",", "whatever", "situation", "arise", "I", "try", "to", "help", "them", "to", "the", "best", "of", "my", "ability", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "And what do you say to him about that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "him", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Well I (inaudible) was to be kind to them and treat them nice and yeah so, it's just difficult situation, you know, I mean dealing with children with matters like that, matters of the heart and I try to give them the best advice possible they can with those situations and I just hope that he listens to me because he's going to make his decisions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "(", "inaudible", ")", "was", "to", "be", "kind", "to", "them", "and", "treat", "them", "nice", "and", "yeah", "so", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "difficult", "situation", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "mean", "dealing", "with", "children", "with", "matters", "like", "that", ",", "matters", "of", "the", "heart", "and", "I", "try", "to", "give", "them", "the", "best", "advice", "possible", "they", "can", "with", "those", "situations", "and", "I", "just", "hope", "that", "he", "listens", "to", "me", "because", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "make", "his", "decisions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]